Oh!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Well, you know, I was thinking of moving
the couch over here.
Why would you want to do that?
So that there would be a decent place
for me to sit.
Great.
There is a decent place.
And your lap does not count.
Hey, come on, help me move this.
No, no, no.
No?
No.
Rosita does not move.
I'm sorry.
Rosita?
As in...
As in Rosita does not move.
Joey, it's just a chair.
What's the big deal?
The big deal is that it is the
exact equal distance from the bathroom to the
kitchen and it's at the perfect angle so
you don't get any glare coming off of
Stevie.
Stevie the TV?
Is there a problem?
No.
Oh, what does he know?
Come on, Rosita.
Us Chico's got to stick together.
Ow!
You bitch.
Hey, you know what's weird?
After you guys get married, when you introduce
me to people, you're going to have to
say, this is my brother-in-law, Ross.
Not my friend, Ross.
Brother-in-law, Ross.
That's weird, isn't it?
Couldn't I just say, this is Ross?
Sure, do whatever you want.
Hey, Ross.
So, I was checking out the real estate
section.
Yeah?
Look at this.
Oh, it looks like Mom and Dad's house.
Oh, it even has a tree with a
broken limb out front.
And the window in the attic.
Oh, my God!
What?
What happened to the window in the attic?
I can't believe Mom and Dad are selling
the house.
I can't believe they didn't even tell us.
I can't believe I still don't know what
happened to the window in the attic.
Hello, Dad.
Monica and I just saw the house in
the paper.
Guess we're surprised.
Who did you leave a message with?
Sorry!
Joey, Joey, I'm so sorry.
I told you not to move it.
Mitch, how would you feel if, say, I
wanted to move your mom, okay?
And you said don't, and I did it
anyway, and her pad fell off.
Okay, come on.
Joey, I'll buy you a new one, all
right?
We'll go down to the store right now,
and we'll get you a new chair.
She's not even called yet.
Don't you think Rosita would have wanted you
to move on?
I mean, you know, she did always put
your comfort first.
That's true.
Okay, you ready?
Yeah.
I don't want Stevie to see her like
this.
I can't believe we have to say goodbye
to the house we grew up in.
Man, some stranger's gonna be living in my
room.
Well, after 15 years of Mom and Dad
keeping it as a shrine to you, it's
time the velvet ropes came down.
I kept your room for a while.
Oh, please, Dad turned my room into a
gym 20 minutes after I moved out.
I gotta say, a tanning bed and a
stack of Victoria's Secret catalogs, not a gym.
Come on, you know they love you.
As much as they love you?
I was their firstborn.
They thought she was barren.
It's not my fault.
Hey.
I hate this year.
What's wrong with this year?
Well, okay, it's already February, and I've only
given two massages, and they were both the
worst tippers in the world.
That was me and Ross.
Oh, that's right.
Hey, you know, if you want to pick
up some extra cash, some friends of mine
made good money in college doing telemarketing.
Oh, that's a great idea.
You're really good on the phone.
Yeah, and, yeah, it would probably be better
than the last telephone job I had.
You know, I probably won't have to say
spank as much.
What?
Oh, yeah, like you never called.
So, basically, this is very easy.
You read from the script, and you try
to sell as much toner as you possibly
can.
Okay, I can do that.
Oh, by the way, I love my office.
Why don't we do a trial run?
Oh, okay.
Um, all right.
Hi, this is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
Can I speak to your supply manager, please?
I'm the supply manager.
Um, okay, I'd like to talk to you
about your toner needs.
We don't need any toner.
Oh, okay, well, I'm sorry to bother you.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, you're right, this is easy.
Okay, what was wrong with that call?
Oh, well, all right.
Um, no offense, but you were kind of
rude.
They're always going to tell you they don't
need toner, but that's okay.
Because whatever they say, you can find the
answer to it here in the script.
Oh.
So, I think you're ready to sell toner.
Do you have any last questions?
No.
Oh, wait, yes, I do.
I do have one question.
What is toner?
Oh, wait.
Joe.
Full bag.
Beer's still cold.
Something terrible must have happened here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Stevie, I was never here.
Dad?
I'm here.
Hey.
God, it seems like just yesterday you guys
used to come out to watch me work.
Dad, we can't believe you're selling the house.
Well, it's time for a new family to
start their memories here.
And hopefully, they're check'll clear before they find
the crack in the foundation and the asbestos
in the ceiling.
Let's just grab our stuff and get the
hell out of here.
I'm sorry we can't store your childhood things
anymore.
Oh, it's okay.
I can't wait to see everything again.
All the memories.
Well, I don't know what's in the boxes
down here, but I do know that there
are six or seven easy-bake ovens in
the attic.
I used to love to play restaurant.
Eh, not as much as you love to
play uncooked batter eater.
It is unreasonable to expect a child to
wait for a light bulb to cook brownies.
So, I think your boxes are over here.
Oh, great.
Hey.
Dad, whose cigarettes are these?
I don't know.
They must be your mother's.
But please, please don't ask her.
I'll throw these away.
Cool, Dad!
My report cards.
Hey, check this out.
Dad, math, A.
Science, A.
History, A.
Gym.
Ooh, my rock polisher.
Oh, look, look.
There's your old makeup kit.
It's a clown kit.
Clown kit.
Well, the white seems to be untouched.
Uh-oh.
What?
Do you know how the garage door opens?
The garage floods every spring.
How are you ever going to sell this
place?
I think I accidentally used Monica's boxes to
keep the water away from the Porsche.
Oh, no.
Dad.
What the?
Oh, God.
Everything's ruined.
Dad, she's going to be crushed.
You don't secretly smoke, do you?
No.
So it's just your mother, then.
This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
Can I speak to your supply manager, please?
Earl, thanks.
Hi, Earl.
This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
I'd like to talk to you about your
toner needs.
I don't need any toner.
I'm hearing what you're saying, but at our
prices, everyone needs toner.
Not me.
May I ask why?
You want to know why?
I surely do.
Okay.
I don't need any toner because I'm going
to kill myself.
Um, is that because you're out of toner?
Okay, so no toner today.
Thanks anyway.
Bye-bye.
No, no.
Wait, wait.
I can't just let you hang up.
Please talk to me.
Well, I only had one thing to do
today.
I guess I could push it back.
Yeah.
Now, why do you want to kill yourself?
It's just that I've been working for ten
years now at this meaningless, dead-end job,
and nobody here even knows that I exist.
Chandler?
I'm sorry?
Look, I'm sure that people know you exist.
Oh, yeah?
I work in a cubicle surrounded by people.
I've been talking to you for five minutes
now about killing myself, and no one's even
looked up from their desk.
Hang on.
Hey, everybody.
I'm going to kill myself.
I'll get back to you.
I got nothing.
Wait.
Hey, Marge.
Nothing.
A chair.
Now, if anybody asks, your name is Rosita.
Come on, Joey.
I just bought you a new chair.
The most expensive one in the store.
Hey, you know what I was thinking?
We could name her Francette.
Francette?
What is she, a couch?
Poor thing.
Cut down on her pride.
Joey, the new chair will be here in
an hour.
Maybe we should actually move Rosita out of
here, you know?
Start the healing process.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Maybe I'll take her down to the incinerator.
It's going to be so sad.
And kind of cool.
Oh.
She's healed.
That's weird.
No, it's not weird.
It's a miracle.
It's not a miracle, Joey.
I'm sure there's some explanation.
Oh, there is.
If you want something enough and your heart
is pure wonders, things can happen.
Joey, I really don't...
Can you tell me how this happened?
Well, no.
Miracle.
No, you know what?
Maybe somebody came in here and fixed it.
Or something.
Someone like an angel?
That's right, Joey.
The chair angel came in and healed your
chair.
Get your non-believer ass out of my
Yeah.
Well, she'll understand, right?
It's not like I did it on purpose.
Dad, that won't matter to her.
Look, all my stuff is safe and dry.
And all her stuff is growing new stuff.
See, this is exactly the kind of thing
that makes her think you guys love me
more than you love her.
Oh, my God.
Does she really think that?
Well, can you blame her?
I don't know.
I suppose we may have favored you unconsciously.
You were a medical marvel.
The doctor said your mother could...
Dad, Dad.
I don't want to hear about it.
Really?
Well, not right now.
Okay, look.
Monica came here for some memories.
Damn it, we're going to give her some.
Okay, grab...
Grab some empty boxes, okay?
We'll take stuff from mine and whatever we
can pass off as hers, we'll put them
in there.
Right.
Like, uh...
Here, like this.
She could have made this, right?
And this?
She could have won this?
This could have been hers.
Sure.
Oh, here.
What about this?
Your makeup kit?
I'd feel better.
I am so psyched I kept this chair
for myself.
Yeah, me too.
Hey, how's the, uh, how's the miracle chair?
Fine.
I know.
Wow, you know that this thing has speakers
in the headrest?
No, really?
Yeah.
You can hook it up to your TV
and you get radio.
My chair heals itself.
Earl, you're not hearing me.
All I'm saying is that you're not alone,
alright?
Everybody hates the people they work with.
Hey, guy.
Wait, what was that?
That sounded like someone being nice to you.
No, that's just the, hey, guy, guy.
He says that to everybody.
He's the worst.
I'd like to take him with me.
Alright, so, Earl, let's just forget about the
people at the office, okay?
There's gotta be someone else in your life
that's worth sticking around for.
What about, what about your family or friends
or maybe a girlfriend?
Yeah, right.
Oh, sorry, boyfriend.
Oh, God.
No, whatever, anything.
Hey, guy.
Yeah, he's gotta go.
Okay, I should, I should probably be getting
back to my thing now.
See ya.
No, I'm not finished yet.
Don't, don't you dare hang up on me.
The new girl's good.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
I just whipped us up some easy baked
treats.
They should be ready in about three days.
That's a good one.
You hear that, Ross?
Three days.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, this will make a great memory.
So, which boxes are mine?
Oh, these.
These are yours right here.
Okay.
Oh, a coloring book.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, you love that thing.
You always had it with you.
You never went anywhere without, without that coloring
book.
Really?
Wow.
Looks like I had some trouble staying inside
the lines.
Nuh-uh.
An old glove?
Oh, yeah.
You love that glove.
You took it every place you went.
But you never went any place without the
glove.
Wow, look at this.
I can't believe I even fit into this
shirt.
Oh, this is yours.
I don't know how that got in there.
This isn't mine.
Hey, this isn't my stuff.
Ross.
These are your boxes.
Where are my boxes?
Uh, your boxes are, um...
What?
Dad?
Well, the garage flooded, sweetie, and it ruined
everything in your boxes.
I'm sorry.
Just mine?
I'm afraid so.
So, why, why wasn't Ross's stuff ruined?
And if you say the words medical marvel,
I'm going to easy bake your head.
I'm sorry.
I used your boxes to divert water away
from the Porsche.
So, wait, Ross's stuff is fine, but I
have no memories because you wanted to keep
the bottom two edges of your car away
from water?
Well, there was also leaves and gook and
stuff.
I can't believe this.
Screw it.
I'm having one.
Hey, Chandler.
Hey.
How would you like to sit in a
chair that fully reclines, has a rolling massage,
and speakers in the headrest?
Yeah, I'd love to, but I've tried that
so many times, they won't even let me
in the store anymore.
Well, what if I told you that you
could do it in my apartment?
Are you telling me that you bought the
chair that is making all other lounge systems
obsolete the chair that SIT Magazine called Chair
of the Year?
I just purchased the Lazy Boy E-Kleiner
3000.
Well, that's awesome.
That's great.
What made you do it?
Well, it's a long story, but I broke
Joey's chair.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You broke Joey's chair?
Yeah.
I thought I broke Joey's chair.
That's why I replaced it with mine.
Oh, that's how it got fixed.
What did you think?
That elves came in and fixed it?
No.
Angels.
I'm getting my chair back.
What?
Wait.
Well, looks like it wasn't healed after all.
So, I guess this chair is mine now.
Joey, you broke my chair.
Your chair?
Yeah, he thought he broke your chair, so
he switched the chairs.
So, there was no miracle?
No, Joe, no miracle.
Oh, no, this is devastating.
My faith is shaken.
I'm so glad I have the new chair
to get me through this difficult time in
my life.
Uh-uh.
Nice try, but you don't get that chair
anymore, all right?
That is my chair now.
You can sit on my lap.
No, I take that back.
I think I should get the chair.
Wait.
How do you figure it?
Because you broke a chair, and you broke
a chair.
The only one here that hasn't broken a
chair is me.
No, no, no.
This chair's not going anywhere.
Well, where's the logic in that?
The logic is that there are two of
us, and we are both strong enough to
break a chair in half.
So, Joey breaks my chair, and I get
nothing.
That's right.
What are you guys, like a gang or
something?
Yeah, we are.
We're the Cobras.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me where I could find
Earl?
He's the supply manager here.
Sorry, I don't know any Earl.
I'm right here!
Hello.
I'm Phoebe.
Phoebe?
The lady who sells toner?
Um, look, you can't kill yourself.
Look, um, I really appreciate you coming down.
No, no, I can't, I can't let you
do it.
Why?
Because it was fate that made me call
you today.
I thought it was toner.
No, think about it, okay?
This isn't even my regular job, okay?
And my first day on the job, you're
my first call.
And somebody else might have hung up on
you, but I wouldn't do that, because I
know about this stuff.
My mom killed herself.
Really?
Yes.
How?
I'm not gonna give you tips.
Look, don't you see that this all came
together so that I could stop you from
doing this?
Couldn't it just be a coincidence?
No, it's fate.
That doesn't really seem like enough to be
fate.
Oh, well, um, okay, here's a weird thing.
My mother was also a supply manager.
I'm actually the office manager.
Oh, my God, so was she!
And get this, okay?
Your name is Earl, right?
Her name was Pearl.
P-Earl.
Was there anything else?
Sure.
Um, where are you from?
Philadelphia.
Oh, my God, so was she!
Oh, I've got, I've got goose, I've got
goosebumps.
Really?
Well, you know, I'm wearing layers and it's
warm.
Yeah, yeah.
But if you look, okay, these jerks might
not care about you, but the universe does,
and that says a lot.
Did you hear that?
I don't need you guys to care about
me because the universe cares!
The whole universe!
I really wish they'd care just a little
bit more.
You know, I don't think it's you.
This is a freaky place.
Hey, guys!
Oh, no, it's you.
Yeah.
Oh, this is terrible.
Everything is destroyed.
Look at this.
It obviously meant enough for me to save
it, and I don't even know what it
is.
It's still soft.
What do you think this is?
Well, I think it was a mouse.
Aah!
Oh, my God!
How are you, honey?
How do you think I am?
You've wrecked all my childhood memories.
You love Ross more than me, and I
just rubbed a dead mouse on my face.
Sweetheart, we love you just as much as
Ross.
Now, I'm sorry about everything that happened, and
I'll probably never be able to make it
up to you, but here's a start.
What's this?
It's the key to my Porsche.
Well, the key to your Porsche.
What?
What?!
I've been thinking of getting rid of it,
and I was driving it the other day,
and I saw my reflection in a store
window.
Your mother's right.
I do look like an ass.
You're giving me your Porsche?
You're kidding me, right?
Well, wait a minute.
I mean, a couple of stupid boxes get
wet, and she gets a Porsche?
Why don't we take it for a spin?
All right.
Well, what about me?
I'm a medical marvel!
Oh, yeah.
Uh...
Eh?
Uh-uh.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Do you know what happened to Chandler's Barca
lounger?
Oh, yeah, Joey broke it and had to
get rid of it.
Are you kidding?
I get a Porsche and the Barca lounger's
gone?
This is the best day ever!